[
    {
        "category":"CSS",
        "type":"multiple",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "question":" Which of the following selector matches the name of any element type?",
        "correct_answer":" The Universal Selector",
        "incorrect_answers":[ 
        " The Type Selector"," The Descendant Selector"," The Class Selector"
        ]
    },
    {
      "category": "CSS",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "In CSS what does 'color:red;' can be called as?",
      "correct_answer": "Declaration",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Ruler", "Selector", "Design"]
    },
    {
      "category": "CSS",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What CSS stands for?",
      "correct_answer": "Cascading Style Sheets",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Color Style Sheets",
        "Cascade Sheets Style",
        "Cascade Style Sheet"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "CSS",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which of the following selector selects all elements of E that have the attribute attr that end with the given value?",
      "correct_answer": "E[attr$=value]",
      "incorrect_answers": ["E[attr^=value]", "E[attr*=value]", " none of the mentioned"]
    },
    {
      "category": "CSS",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which of the following selector selects the elements that are checked?",
      "correct_answer": ":checked",
      "incorrect_answers": ["E ~ F", "::after", "none of the mentioned"]
    },
    {
      "category": "CSS",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which of the following selector selects an element that has no children?",
      "correct_answer": ":empty",
      "incorrect_answers": [":nochild", ":inheritance", ":no-child"]
    },
    {
      "category": "CSS",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which of the following selector selects the element that is the first child of its parent that is of its type?",
      "correct_answer": ":first-of-type",
      "incorrect_answers": [":last-child","::first-line","::first-letter"]
    },
    {
      "category": "CSS",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which of the following selector selects elements that do not match the selector s?",
      "correct_answer": ":not(s)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        ":!(s)",
        ":nth-child(s)",
        " none of the mentioned"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "CSS",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "All object have prototypes.\n\n ",
      "correct_answer": "false",
      "incorrect_answers": ["true"]
    },
    {
      "category": "CSS",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which of the following selector selects the element that is the first child of its parent that is of its type?",
      "correct_answer": ":first-of-type",
      "incorrect_answers": [":last-child","::first-line","::first-letter"]
    }
  ]
  